{
  "categories": [
    {
      "category": "Popular Questions",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is Lorem Ipsum?",
          "answer": "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where does it come from?",
          "answer": "Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s."
        },
        {
          "question": "Why do we use it?",
          "answer": "It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where can I get some?",
          "answer": "There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available."
        },
        {
          "question": "Why do we use it?",
          "answer": "It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where can I get some?",
          "answer": "There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Plans & Pricing ",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is Lorem Ipsum?",
          "answer": "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where does it come from?",
          "answer": "Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s."
        },
        {
          "question": "Why do we use it?",
          "answer": "It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where can I get some?",
          "answer": "There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available."
        },
        {
          "question": "Why do we use it?",
          "answer": "It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where can I get some?",
          "answer": "There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available."
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "More Important ",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is Lorem Ipsum?",
          "answer": "Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where does it come from?",
          "answer": "Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s."
        },
        {
          "question": "Why do we use it?",
          "answer": "It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where can I get some?",
          "answer": "There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available."
        },
        {
          "question": "Why do we use it?",
          "answer": "It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where can I get some?",
          "answer": "There are many variations of passages of Lorem Ipsum available."
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
